A Guide to the Papers of George Conoly Phillips, 1942-1978
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University Libraries, Old Dominion University
- Community / Civic Memberships and Activities
  - Miscellaneous
    - Sertoma Club, City of Norfolk: A City of the Past, Present, and Future January 29, 1992 (Box-folder 19:11)
    - University of Georgia Alumni Chapter 1967-68 (Box-folder 19:12)
    - VDOT Tunnel Advisors Committee Meeting Nov. 18, 2004 (Box-folder 19:13)
    - VRMA Board of Directors Meeting Oct. 21-23, 1988 (Box-folder 19:14)
- Political Activities
  - Political Correspondence
    - Councilman 1976 (Box-folder 19:15)
    - Letters to Conoly Phillips from Senators 1980s- 1990s (Box-folder 19:16)
    - Political and Civic Correspondence 1942, 1968-73 (Box-folder 19:17)
  - Delegate Listings
    - Delegate Listings I 1978 (Box-folder 19:18)
    - Delegate Listings II 1978 (Box-folder 19:19)
    - Delegate Listings III 1978 (Box-folder 19:20)
    - Delegate Listings IV (not in order) 1978 (Box-folder 19:21)
    - Delegate Listings V (not in order) 1978 (Box-folder 19:22)
    - Delegate Listings VI (not in order) 1978 (Box-folder 19:23)
  - Democratic Mass Meetings
    - Democratic Mass Meetings I 1978 (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Democratic Mass Meetings II 1978 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Virginia Democratic State Convention 1978 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Congressional District Chairmen and Congressional District Organizational Summary 1978 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Committee Elections 2nd, 3rd, 4th, 7th, and 8th Congressional District 1978 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Tidewater Mass Meeting April 15, 1978 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Norfolk City Council Business
    - Annual Budget Concerns June 7, 1977 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Communications 1992 (Box-folder 20:8)
    - Comparative Report of Local Governments (excerpts) June 30, 1990 (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Correspondence: City Manager 1992 (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Correspondence: Interdepartmental 1992 (Box-folder 20:11)
    - Correspondence: Norfolk City Council 1992 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - Current Human Resource Issues Under Review undated (Box-folder 20:13)
    - Department of Utilities, Management, and Operations Report January 7, 2000 (Box-folder 20:14)
    - Employees’ Retirement System 1990 (Box-folder 20:15)
    - Finance and Infrastructure Committee -- Meeting Dec. 20, 1999 (Box-folder 20:16)
    - Finance and Infrastructure Committee -- Review of Operations & Management of the Department of Utilities December 20, 1999 (Box-folder 20:17)
    - Greater Norfolk Corp., Press Release, "Downtown Produces More Benefits Than Costs" December 4, 1991 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - Image Processing System Selection 1991 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - Literacy 1991 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Magazine Articles 1990s (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Management Letter June 30, 1991 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Marina Proposal 1992 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - Norfolk City Council 2000 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - Norfolk Community Services Board, Public Hearing 1992 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Norfolk Review Final Report June 1, 1980 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - A Plan for Downtown Norfolk 2000 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - Quarterly Projection for Period Ending Feb. 29, 1992 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Report on Soviet Sister City Initiative Oct. 29, 1991 (Box-folder 21:12)
    - Services Inventory and Goals and Objectives Feb. 18, 1992 (Box-folder 21:13)
    - Virginia Ports Authority Expansion 2000 (Box-folder 21:14)
  - Sub-series E Norfolk City Council Race
    - Campaign Contributions and Expenditures 1980, 1986 (Box-folder 21:15)
    - Campaign Contributions and Expenditures 1990, 1992 (Box-folder 21:16)
    - Campaign Fund 2002 (Box-folder 21:17)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1976 I (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1976 II (Box-folder 22:2)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1976 III (Box-folder 22:3)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1976 IV (Box-folder 22:4)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1976 V (Box-folder 22:5)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1976 VI (Box-folder 22:6)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1980 I (Box-folder 22:7)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1980 II (Box-folder 22:8)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1980 III (Box-folder 22:9)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1980 IV (Box-folder 22:10)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1986 I (Box-folder 23:1)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1986 II (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1986 III (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1990 (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1992 I (Box-folder 23:5)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1992 II (Box-folder 23:6)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1992 III (Box-folder 23:7)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1992 IV (Box-folder 23:8)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1992 V (Box-folder 23:9)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1992 VI (Box-folder 23:10)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1994 I (Box-folder 24:1)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1994 II (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1994 III (Box-folder 24:3)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1998 I (Box-folder 24:4)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1998 II (Box-folder 24:5)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1998 III (Box-folder 24:6)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 1998 IV (Box-folder 24:7)
    - Norfolk City Council Race 2000 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - Index Cards: City Council Campaign 1986 (Box-folder 25:1)
  - U.S. Senate Campaign 1978
    - Articles: Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 26:1)
    - Biographical Information – Conoly Phillips undated (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Campaign Analysis January 10, 1978 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Campaign Materials undated (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Campaign Notebook undated (Box-folder 26:5)
    - Campaign Notes undated (Box-folder 26:6)
    - Campaign Strategy undated (Box-folder 26:7)
    - Candidacy Paperwork undated (Box-folder 26:8)
    - Congressional District Organizational Summary undated (Box-folder 26:9)
    - Convention Delegate Information undated (Box-folder 26:10)
    - Convention Housing undated (Box-folder 26:11)
    - Correspondence: To Betsy Phillips undated (Box-folder 26:12)
    - Correspondence: To Conoly Phillips undated (Box-folder 26:13)
    - Correspondence: To Delegates undated (Box-folder 26:14)
    - Correspondence: To Democratic Committee Members undated (Box-folder 26:15)
    - Correspondence: To Friend in Christ undated (Box-folder 26:16)
    - Correspondence: To Jerry Tiahrt undated (Box-folder 26:17)
    - Correspondence: To Supporters undated (Box-folder 26:18)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 26:19)
    - Delegate Forms undated (Box-folder 26:20)
    - Democratic Party of Norfolk Notice March 17, 1978 (Box-folder 26:21)
    - Finances undated (Box-folder 26:22)
    - Itineraries undated (Box-folder 26:23)
    - Mailing / Contact Lists I undated (Box-folder 26:24)
    - Mailing / Contact Lists II undated (Box-folder 26:25)
    - Mailing / Contact Lists III undated (Box-folder 26:26)
    - Method of Nomination United States Senate Seat 1978 (Box-folder 26:27)
    - Newsletters featuring Conoly Phillips undated (Box-folder 26:28)
    - Official Election Results 1976 (Box-folder 26:29)
    - Other Candidates undated (Box-folder 26:30)
    - Participating Voter Information undated (Box-folder 26:31)
    - Pledges of Commitment undated (Box-folder 26:32)
    - Press Releases undated (Box-folder 26:33)
    - Stands on Issues undated (Box-folder 26:34)
    - University of Virginia Newsletter: The 1978 Virginia Senatorial Nominating Conventions December 1978 (Box-folder 26:35)
    - Voter Registration undated (Box-folder 27:1)
    - Miscellaneous: Senate Campaign undated (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Miscellaneous Political
    - Admiral Carlisle A.H. Trost Biography undated (Box-folder 27:3)
    - Chesapeake City Council Newsletter undated (Box-folder 27:4)
    - City Council Resolution Recognizing 20 Years of Service June 27, 2002 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - Embassy of the USSR 1989-91 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - Real Estate Holdings Disclosure, Conoly Phillips April 5, 1987 (Box-folder 27:7)
- Personal Information
  - Personal Correspondence
    - Christmas Letters and Lists 1970s, 1980s, 1990s (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Personal Correspondence I November 1968 - January 1972 (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Personal Correspondence II August 1972 - November 1973 (Box-folder 27:10)
  - Education
    - Air Force 1952-55 (Box-folder 27:11)
    - Childhood 1930s – 1940s (Box-folder 27:12)
    - Maury High School 1949 (Box-folder 27:13)
    - Maury High School "Class of 1949" 50th Reunion October 1999 (Box-folder 27:14)
    - University of Georgia 1950-53 (Box-folder 27:15)
  - Family
    - Betsy Ferebee Phillips (Conoly’s Wife) 1970s - 1980s (Box-folder 27:16)
    - Charlotte Phillips (Conoly’s daughter) undated (Box-folder 27:17)
    - Note from Julie (Conoly’s niece) undated (Box-folder 27:18)
  - Finances
    - Financial Records 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 27:19)
    - Stocks / Shares (G. Benson Ferebee, Jr.) 1979 (Box-folder 27:20)
  - Real Estate
    - Deeds to Snug Harbor, NC and Glenn Cove, NC Properties 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 28:1)
    - Walnut Island Property 1971-72 (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Misc. – Handwritten Notes undated (Box-folder 28:3)
    - Notes undated (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Personal Agreements 1950s (Box-folder 28:5)
- Writing and Speeches
  - Writing
    - Higher Education Drafts 1977-78 (Box-folder 28:6)
    - ODU Business Management Papers by Conoly Phillips 1976 (Box-folder 28:7)
    - "Should morals be a priority," Mace and Crown October 24, 1977 (Box-folder 28:8)
  - Speeches
    - Councilman Speeches 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 28:9)
    - Council Speeches (by other people) 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 28:10)
  - Speech Notes and Annotated Source Materials
    - Articles - Integration 1970s (Box-folder 28:11)
    - Articles - Politics 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 28:12)
    - Articles -- Public Schools 1980s (Box-folder 28:13)
    - Notes - Cities 1970s (Box-folder 28:14)
    - Miscellaneous 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 28:15)
- Multimedia
  - Audio Cassettes
    - G. Conoly Phillips, "Springfield, Va 12 Mar 78" March 12, 1978 (Box-folder 29:1)
    - "Introducing Conoly Phillips" undated (Box-folder 29:2)
    - " Men's Prayer Breakfast", Conoly Phillips undated (Box-folder 29:3)
    - G.C. Phillips Authority Sales Mtg. 12/79 December 1979 (Box-folder 29:4)
  - Compact Discs
    - Dealership Design Process, J. Howard Nudell Architects, Inc. Interactive Navigation Tour undated (Box-folder 29:5)
    - Phillips, "A Very Simple Business" Radio Spots 1-15 undated (Box-folder 29:6)
  - Floppy Discs
    - Conoly Logo IBM (1 of 4) undated (Box-folder 29:7)
    - Conoly Logo IBM (2 of 4) undated (Box-folder 29:8)
    - Conoly Logo IBM (3 of 4) undated (Box-folder 29:9)
    - Conoly Logo IBM (4 of 4) undated (Box-folder 29:10)
    - Planet Cars Video Logo undated (Box-folder 29:11)
    - Care and Share, Format (Jiff) undated (Box-folder 29:12)
  - Reel Tapes
    - Leon Shaffer Golnick Advertising, Phillips Lincoln Mercury, Master, 12/18/72 December 18, 1972 (Box-folder 29:13)
    - WTAR Radio, Phillips Lincoln Mercury, Master P undated (Box-folder 29:14)
    - WTAR Radio, Phillips Lincoln Mercury, For ThursA undated (Box-folder 29:15)
    - Phillips Master, from FOG undated (Box-folder 29:16)
  - VHS and Betamax Tapes
    - Council Update with Councilman G. Conoly Phillips (VHS) undated (Box-folder 30:1)
    - City Talk, Featuring G. Conoly Phillips, 10-4-99 (VHS) October 4, 1999 (Box-folder 30:2)
    - Phillips for City Council, TV Spots (VHS) undated (Box-folder 30:3)
    - Conoly Phillips for U.S. Senate edited master of two live TV programs (Betamax) undated (Box-folder 30:4)
    - Christian Broadcasting Network, Live Program #2 (Betamax) undated (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Photographs
    - Aerial Photos undated (Box-folder 31:1)
    - American Motors 1961 (Box-folder 31:2)
    - Automotive Team undated (Box-folder 31:3)
    - Awards undated (Box-folder 31:4)
    - Cars undated (Box-folder 31:5)
    - Conoly Phillips Lincoln Mercury 1950s-1970s (Box-folder 31:6)
    - Cougar undated (Box-folder 31:7)
    - Dealerships 1940s-1990s (Box-folder 31:8)
    - Department photos undated (Box-folder 31:9)
    - Events undated (Box-folder 31:10)
    - Fiat 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 31:11)
    - Ford 1970s-1990s (Box-folder 31:12)
    - Groups of People undated (Box-folder 31:13)
    - Paint Both June 25, 1992 (Box-folder 31:14)
    - Phillips Bros. Rambler 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 31:15)
    - President’s Day Sale 1994 (Box-folder 31:16)
    - Nations Dealer Council 1972 (Box-folder 31:17)
    - Virginia Lottery Winner buys Towncar undated (Box-folder 31:18)
    - City Council Race 1986 (Box-folder 31:19)
    - City Council Race 1992 (Box-folder 31:20)
    - Conoly Phillips Headshots undated (Box-folder 31:21)
    - Councilman undated (Box-folder 31:22)
    - Miscellaneous Political undated (Box-folder 31:23)
    - Senate Campaign Headshots 1978 (Box-folder 31:24)
    - Air Force 1950s (Box-folder 31:25)
    - Conoly and Betsy undated (Box-folder 31:26)
    - Family undated (Box-folder 31:27)
    - School 1940s (Box-folder 31:28)
    - Sports 1950s (Box-folder 31:29)
    - USAF Wyoming 1953-54 (Box-folder 31:30)
    - CBN Business School Luncheon May 1984 (Box-folder 31:31)
- Artifacts
  - undated (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Conoly Phillips Lincoln-Mercury License Plate undated (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Conoly Phillips Lincoln-Mecury, 25th Anniversary Antique / Special Interest Auto Show emblem March 20, 1982 (Box-folder 32:3)
  - Political Button: "Re-Elect U.S. Senator Robertson" undated (Box-folder 32:4)
  - Political Button: "Stovall Clerk of Circuit Court" undated (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Buttons: Conoly Phillips for Council (3) undated (Box-folder 32:6)
- Oversize
  - Black Scrapbook, Phillips Bros. advertisements and articles 1966-70 (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Black Scrapbook, Phillips Bros. Rambler advertisements and articles 1959-65 (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Maroon Scrapbook, Phillips Bros. Lincoln-Mercury advertisements and articles 1967-70 (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Black Scrapbook, Phillips Bros. Rambler, Retailer of the Year Competition 1964 (Box-folder 35:1)
  - Phillips Lincoln Mercury photo letterhead undated (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Conoly Phillips Lincoln Mercury photo undated (Box-folder 35:3)
  - Aerial Photo Conoly Phillips Lincoln Mercury (before) undated (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Aerial Photo Conoly Phillips Lincoln Mercury (after) undated (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Rambler New Car Show, Atlantic City, N.J. 1961 photo 1961 (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Sales Associates and family with George Romney, President, American Motors Corporation, 1960 photo 1960 (Box-folder 35:7)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, Georgia 1952 photo 1952 (Box-folder 35:8)
  - University of Georgia 1951 fraternity photo 1951 (Box-folder 35:9)
  - ODU Master of Business Administration degree, Conoly Phillips December 21, 1976 (Box-folder 35:10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia certification, Conoly Phillips, Member of the City Council July 1, 1986-June 30, 1990 (Box-folder 35:11)
  - “Christianity and the Marketplace,” Conoly Phillips guest speaker, April 7 poster April 7 (Box-folder 35:12)
  - Conoly Phillips Concerned and Dedicated for Norfolk City Council, May 4 poster May 4 (Box-folder 35:13)
  - Re-elect On May 1, Conoly Phillips, City Council poster May 1 (Box-folder 35:14)
  - Conoly Phillips, U.S. Senate Poster undated (Box-folder 35:15)
  - City of Norfolk Electoral Districts and Voting Precincts July 12, 1983 (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Untitled City of Norfolk District Map undated (Box-folder 36:2)